what we had was sacred but maybe it was just meme coded truth and now that i've ghosted
i finally know i glitched something real cause i miss you yeah beta i miss you
Like it's background noise You say you're done, but you're all still
Watches lurking in the replay void I don't understand if you ever cared
I only catch static Bad vibes and panic
So I turn my mic on Turn the gain up loud
into a vape cloud dream
some of us hover where the drama was born
haunted since the day we logged on
this isn't shade, it's confession
I thought I was immune to connection
yeah you called me clever
I called it survival
now we're both influencers of denial
you said I was not
I got Nick Johnson here Nick Johnson's here
What is Nick so fuck with Nick still likes me? No one should like me anymore
I'm a bad bad person. I'm bad
No one should like me everyone unsubscribe from me
Don't like me anymore. I'm just a bad person. I am I'm I'm not good
I'm not good for YouTube. I'm not good for anybody
I'm bad I
Only hear what I want to I only spurred when I want to Nick was still there. Thank you Nick. I
Love you guys, so I
Can't leave that's why I can't leave I love you
So you want my fire, no I don't crave it
But I light it, step into my storm
No I won't fight it, I'll ignite it
Keep it strange divine, no mourning after no rewind
This feels like a glitch in fate, we don't heal we just create
Be the kind of soul you can only touch in the astral
Yeah, we don't ride waves, we become the tidal
Call it devotion, maybe we should draw emotion
I can be your vice, your omen
You're not the only one
you don't need to call in sick you're already inside the mystic call it devotion maybe we
should drop emotion i can be
wish tonight someone said make a panterra song can I do that might even so
we're gonna have to make one panterra song I know this deep egg I'm sorry
burning joint Nick so Nick my cutie Nick is my cutie patootie okay he just is
I can do one more song yes I can't
Can I do it? I don't know
Yes, I can't
Hold on
I'm too drunk to do it. Maybe I
Tried
No, it's it's happening. It's gonna happen
Hey there Nick. I'm sorry guys. You'll be mad at me. Don't be mad at me. Don't be mad at me. Don't be mad at me
I'm sorry. I can't like
My brain is going in too many directions right now. It's going in too many directions. Hold on
I'm gonna make the song from Nick though Nick one of the song
Because you know Nick's been here since the beginning. He's my he's my bro
Nick you're my bro
I'm sorry guys
I'm sorry guys Nick you there
Have another song for Nick
Nick
Thank you just for being my friends
Hey, no one should be my friend. I'm a bad bad person
Bad person
But I got one for Nick
Are you still there Nick?
I'm trying.
Did you just say Hitler? It's okay.
It's okay.
I don't think anyone's offended.
I have a half-Jewish panel.
I can't offend them with anything.
Maybe I'm half-Jewish. I don't know.
Probably.
I wish.
Jewish. Ah, stupid shit.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Let's see if I got it. Hold
Nick I'm gonna try I promise I'll try
I'm just too drunk. I'm so drunk right now. I don't know if I can do it
Can I do it?
Yeah, I can't I
Did it. Okay. I did it. I did it 32. Okay. I'm gonna do it Nick you wanted a song
You better not leave you better not leave
Just give me a minute Nick Nick give me one minute you need your song it's Pantera
It's Pantera
Okay
I'm sorry I'm too drunk right now. I shouldn't get this drunk
I shouldn't. I can't help it. I'm just drunk. I'm a drunk drunk. Okay, hold on. I'm almost
there, Nick. Nick, can you wait a minute? I promise I'll get you your song. I promise.
Cuz Nick I love you if I have like one ounce of sobriety left it's going towards the song
Okay, that was okay, so Nick I did it. I did it. Okay. You want it you asked for it
It's gonna take another minute more
This is for Nick Johnson guys
Nick Johnson, you know, he's been there for me since the fucking beginning
Wow, and I even trusted him on it just to
Wrote my panel. He never caused me a problem. He never did. He was always a good person always
He's that's funny. How many how many characters has he done for my show like over a hundred?
He was he's been in drag. He's been
So and I'm sorry Nick. Why did I do this for you before? I don't know why
But Nick this one's for you
Okay
It's less of my spirit tonight. I had like just a little bit left. I had like a tiny little bit of spirit
But you know what a tiny little tiny little bit of spirit
Can do miracles and so Nick you big random miracle tonight. You've been great in a miracle
You asked for Pantera
psyche song
Did you ask for that? Yeah, you did. Okay, so I'm gonna keep my promise Nick. This one is for you
It's for only you, okay
Okay, Nick asked for it Nick got it, okay
Nick
You know, I love you, right? You know, I love you. I'm a little bit drunk. Okay, but I'm gonna play for Nick
Nick, this one's for you.
Soda, chaos, welcome to the feet.
The grit is alive, the mind is bleeding.
Awesome.
Steal scream black mirror eyes, you talk divine while the signal dies
Born in static, forged in flame, every troll got a goddamn name
Psyche in the towel, storm in his head, tarot on fire, the spirits are fed
Father of madness, the cat daddy kink, the lords at his feet let the panther sink
Every stream's a blaze
A panel full of chaos, ghosts in the chat
Big pipes barking, Gotti swinging the bat
Hexes and hexes, they're all th-
We're going to have an amazing day.
more like me
Hey guys, I just want to say that to you before I go to bed.
Hey, I love you. Nancy, I love you. Nick, I love you.
My buddies, my buddies, don't forget.
Ever need a place to stay in Los Angeles?
I love you guys. You stay here. Love you.
She whispered her name in the temples of night.
Golden wings glowed in the candlelight.
Crowds came running just to see the flame,
but envy was the price of fame.
And now he stands where the echoes fall,
with tarot in hand hearing every call.
From praise to venom in the same breath said,
burns gold, not red